p-a-r-s-i-e-r google it up what is that
oh geez
hey guys welcome to stir crazy the show
that looks better than it smells
you know my guest today from saturday
night live duck tales and his new comedy
central series low fee
bobby moynihan hey bobby what's up man
how are you good to see you
good to see you uh congratulations on
the new series thank you so much
i hear wolfie is your passion project i
feel like anytime somebody has a passion
project
that says a lot about them what it is
this is about a
wee dealing manatee correct bobby
[Laughter]
what does this say about you oh it means
i like to have a good time with my
friends
in animated form i love manatees um
i enjoy weed dealers and chatting with
them
i noticed uh in the first couple
episodes lofi this manatee has a human
girlfriend
yes becca um
how does that work exactly what love
well i guess i don't want to extrapolate
into the physical realm
but yeah don't it's not none that's none
of your business
that's love it's between becca and loafy
why manatee of all animals to be a weed
dealer
cause look at them what don't you think
they're they might be weed dealers you
don't know
do you have a dream person to smoke weed
with do you i mean do you have like
mount rushmore celebrity weed
enthusiasts you know
wow the seth rogens i mean yeah willie
nelson would be great seth rogen
yeah snoop dogg i would love to smoke
with you i
almost did i came close to once how do
you come
close to that what happened one of his
buddies was like hey come on let's make
it happen
and then i got there they were like he's
gone
so i i guess that's close right you've
actually played a number of you've
voiced the number of animals
yes tell me about it are you typecast do
you feel like when you oh yeah
i played i've i've played several dogs
and
several crabs
dogs and crabs i got cornered you've
also cast a number of uh
exceptional actors as various animals in
this
show yeah let me name for you a
prominent movie star you tell me what
kind of animal you would cast them as i
like this
[Applause]
let's go with the big one tom cruise
what does tom cruise play in loafie or
any animated show
he'd he would be a meerkat playing
a lemur action star run dive off a cliff
gets stops like this right before he
hits the ground just like in mission
impossible
charlize theron what do we want what
animal do we want to see heroes
cheetah probably probably a cheetah
or
oh we lost the connection bobby a bug
i was i was just really thinking about
it well that was
the most seriously you've taken a
question from me in this whole
conversation
uh vin diesel wow yeah
maybe maybe a sloth whoa hey he's a very
quick and agile man why should he be a
sloth give him something to do he's an
actor
that's true sorry i didn't mean to get i
got a little too angry at you
for four vin diesel let's appeal to the
to the youths out there
zendaya the lovely zendaya yes for the
children
maybe a little unicorn oh
the only one of her or like a buffalo
why not like a maybe a buffalo
maybe a half buffalo half unicorn oh
dude i think we just wrote a pixar movie
with a unicorn horn the ugliest unicorn
we call
it i'll see you at the oscars we play a
game here on sir crazy called quaran
team i'm gonna name you a character
maybe you've played maybe you're
associated with
you tell me if you want them on your
quarantine if you want them in the
bunker with you right now
okay wow
[Applause]
drunk uncle do you want drunk uncle
living with you during quarantine
no what about guy fieri would he be
useful
yeah i mean for cooking reasons alone
and and
if you lose power you can uh heat
yourself on his shirts
uh classic snl sketch what about tom
hanks david s pumpkins
yes yeah well he's okay now yeah he
won't i won't get it from him right
the character and tom yeah exactly
who's that that's my skeleton from david
s pumpkins how about let's go some loafy
characters
okay sure loafy be a good friend in
quarantine
absolutely are you kidding me yeah first
of all
he's got a nice little tank you could
swim around in so you can do laps and
get exercise and just chill
he has a microwave his son is adorable
speaking of his son what about beef ron
function's voices
the best is i think top five people of
all time i would want to be stranded
slash anything with might be ron punches
i think he's a really good
person and he looks strong too i feel
like we could build a house together um
every house needs a horny monkey in
there what about scrooge would scrooge
be a good uh
housemate right now scrooge not a monkey
wait what
i know it got i'm realizing a flaw
i accidentally cut the line where we say
that he is a tarsier come again he is a
tarsier
a t-a-r i don't know what it is
i know i know but i'm spelling it
p-a-r-s-i-e-r
google it up what is that
oh jesus it's monkey-ish it might even
be a monkey
i have no idea uh i have some
provocative would you rather questions
for you bobby you ready
uh sure
would you rather hear what's in an
animal's head all the time or hear
what's in humans heads
oh boy am i allowed to have follow-up
questions
i mean like sure
i don't want to take up your time you
want to know
i was going to say am i the first person
to be bestowed this
you are the only person that has then
definitely animals
firefox well because if no one's ever
spoken to an animal before or known an
animal's thoughts then i think that
would be helpful to the universe instead
of being like
now i know what frank really thinks of
me
okay fair enough thank you would you
rather live your life as a duck
or a manatee oh that's rough
um no a manatee i know the answer it's a
manatee
just it just well because you said duck
and my first thought went to louie from
ducktales
and i realized but you mean the animal
not like a rich
anthropomorphic lazy yeah yeah bobby
before we go i have an oldie but a
goodie for you you ready to play some
trades
i think so
i should warn you i am the world's worst
charades player so good luck with this
all right i'm the world's best so
yeah okay that's virtually impossible
four words first word
no not the yes oh that was correct
what hey who's it one i told you i was
shitty at this
okay four words and i'm correct yes
you're staring stare because i'm
thinking oh sorry
second word
it's not a monkey it's it's it's it's
it's it's the word you told me about
that i've never heard before
it's it's a tarsier it's a
it's a big eyed okay scrooge
scrooge is the second word
yeah something screwed something
something
third word um um
you're chewing tobacco you're you're
taking a bite
uncle scrooge's coin ball that is very
difficult that is a very specific
elaborate clue
yeah i had to i had to resort to visual
clues
i'm probably got one word right actually
four
is it the fourth of july i'm just
kidding four words
um
driving cab driver
uh cabbie
eating uh chauffeur driving
kind of like dr sounds like driving
it is driving and you're wrong
hair uh conan o'brien bart simpson
slim jim's like me eating
oh dopey that's the worst part of
charades is when people look
so disappointed in that
they're just like i'm a terrible person
and so is the young person trying
it really breaks my spirit it's the
worst game ever
it was diners drive-ins and dives and
things and stuff and i was doing guy
fieri
why didn't you just say triple do you
just say three d's and i would have been
like triple d's and we would have been
outside having beers already
or google a picture of guy piety and
show it to me
that's what i did okay smarty pants oh
this is
tense well bobby congratulations on the
new show
thank you so much thank you
uh everybody needs to check out loafy it
is the best animated show about a weed
dealing manatee i've ever seen
that is that is a true sentence
uh here's so many more of them and many
more bizarre conversations like this
bobby it's good to see you
i thought you said to here's to mandy
moore in them and i was like you're damn
right here's to mandy moore and all of
them
this one goes out to mandy moore our
biggest fan of stir crazy out there
we love you mandy congratulations on
loafie everybody should check it out in
comedy central's youtube page
thank you so much yeah go check it out
now
you